Young. Beautiful. Deadly.
Savages is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Oliver Stone.
Pot growers Ben and Chon face off against the Mexican drug
cartel who kidnapped their shared girlfriend.
Chon, played by Taylor Kitsch.
Ophelia "O" Sage, played by Blake Lively.
Ben, played by Aaron Taylor-Johnson.
Dennis, played by John Travolta.
Elena, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Lado, played by Benicio del Toro.
Savages is a 2012 American action thriller film directed by Oliver Stone.
Its screenplay, written by Stone, Don Winslow and Shane
Salerno, is based on Winslow's 2010 novel.
It stars Taylor Kitsch, Blake Lively, Aaron Taylor-Johnson, Benicio del
Toro, Demián Bichir, Salma Hayek, and John Travolta.
The film follows two cannabis growers, Chon, an ex-Navy SEAL, and Ben, who are best friends, as
they confront the Mexican drug cartel that kidnapped their shared girlfriend.
The film was released by Universal Pictures on July 6, 2012, to mixed
reviews, and grossed $83 million worldwide on a $45 million budget.
The film explores themes of explosive, widow,
american abroad, eye gouging, dea agent.
The tone is emotional and intense.